<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">OPSC7312 Assignment 2</string>
    <string name="current_address">Address:</string>
    <string name="question1">Question 1</string>
    <string name="question2">Question 2</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="message">Message:</string>
    <string name="send_sms">Send SMS</string>
    <string name="location">Location:</string>
    <string name="send">Send Location To:</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to my assignment 2 application, click on the buttons below or use the menu to launch the required activity</string>
    <string name="country">Country:</string>
    <string name="suburb">Suburb:</string>
    <string name="postcode">Code:</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="student_details">
       Student Name: Gareth Price\n
       Student Number: 11044620\n
       Course: DISD\n
       Module: OPSC 7312
    </string>
    <string name="q1_help_info">If you would like to know the addresses of places you visit or as you drive by them then this
    is the app for you! start up the application and wait for your position to be found, once your location has been determined
    your location will be zoomed into and the address will display beneath the map, you can also see your position in real time
    as you move from place to place so you will know exactly where you are.
    </string>
        <string name="q2_help_info">With this application you can send your current location to anyone in your contacts, use it if
            you are lost, needing help or someone is trying to find you.This application uses GPS in order to find your exact location
            and provide pin point accuracy.How it works: once your location has been determined the contacts text field will become activated
            and you can start typing the name of the contact you want to send your location to, the application will start prompting you with suggestions
            based on your input. you can then type in an optional message to your contact, if you leave the text field blank then a default message will
            be sent with your location. Pop up messages will display when the message has been sent and delivered.
    </string>
    <string name="q1_about_info">Create an Android App that will allow a user to find the mobile phone’s current location using the GPS Location Provider.
        Using the Geocoder, you can determine the street address of your current location. Update the street address whenever the device moves.
    </string>
        <string name="q2_about_info">Using Question 1 above as a guideline, you are now required to create an application that combines the use of GPS (location based) and SMS technology.
        You may conceptualise, design and code your own app based on your own idea. Try to make your GPS/ SMS app useful to a specific business, to non-profit organisation (NGO), or to education.
    </string>



</resources>
